YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com
■
时间轴： godwuwen
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
翻译： Vero  非燕  阿蘅阿蘅  猫中之王
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
校对： YY  YY 的贤内赛    后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第十八集
孩子们  2012年伊始有点混乱
Kids, 2012 started out kind of crazy.
巴尼遇见了一个叫昆茵的女孩
Barney met a girl named Quinn,
凯文收回对罗宾的求婚
Kevin unproposed to Robin,
我告诉罗宾
I told Robin...
我爱你  罗宾
I love you, Robin.
当我问她
When I asked if she
是否爱我的时候  她说
loved me back, she said...
不爱
No.
马修告诉罗宾
Marshall told Robin...
你还是搬出去吧You got to move out.
罗宾照办了
And Robin did.
我现在甚至不敢去开她卧室的门
I can't even open her bedroom door anymore.
我干嘛这么多愁善感
Why do I have to be so sensitive?
我不知道  兄弟
I don't know, bro.
看看我和那个叫昆茵的小妞
Look at me and that Quinn chick.
我就从来不会念叨着说
You don't hear me prattling on
她的笑容有多迷人
about how beautiful her smile is,
她的长发有多像蜜糖色的绸缎般顺滑
how her hair is like a waterfall of honey-colored silk,
她的双眼有多像被旭日的光芒
how her eyes are like a warm South Sea
亲吻着和煦的南海
kissed by the fire and gold of sunrise.
我连她长什么样都不记得了
I don't even remember what she looks like.
哥们  显然你喜欢她
Dude, you obviously like her.
你不能从字里行间听出来吗  泰德
Can't you read between the lines, Ted?
显然我喜欢她
I obviously like her.
这种事怎么会发生在我身上
How did this happen to me?
我什么时候变得又娘又痴情了
When did I become such a gooey romantic?
我觉得这样挺好的
Look, I think it's healthy
你对一个女人产生真感情
that you have real feelings for a woman
而不是只当成她当成玩物
instead of just seeing her as an object.
换吗
Switch?
当然
Sure.
但是为什么是昆茵呢
But why Quinn?
我是说  你和她过了一晚
I mean, you spent one night with her,
她还有点刻薄
and she was kind of mean.
我们就是心有灵犀
We just connected.
无论感情上  理智上  精神上
Emotionally, intellectually, spiritually.
就是说床技一流吗
So, mind-blowing sex?
刻骨铭心啊
Mind-blowing sex!
完事后一小时  我都还是斗鸡眼
For an hour afterwards, I couldn't uncross my eyes.
这样超赞的  因为我再来第二轮的时候
Which was awesome, because when I went back for seconds,
就像在跟一对双胞胎玩三人行
it was like having a three-way with twins.
那就打给她吧
So... call her.
如果我知道怎么联系她  早就打了
I would if I knew how to get in touch with her,
可我没她电话  我都快疯了
but I can't, and it's driving me crazy.
我放眼望去  看到的都是她的身影
Everywhere I look, I see her.
我看见她走在街上
I see her walking on the street;
看见她去商店购物
I see her shopping in the store;
看见她在那跳钢管舞
I see her dancing on that pole.
我也看见她在那儿跳钢管舞
I see her dancing on that pole, too.
我的天  那是昆茵
Oh, my God, that's Quinn.
先生们  掌声欢迎卡玛
Gentlemen, give it up for Karma.
我真很感激你们收留我
I really appreciate you guys taking me in.
我现在无家可归了
I mean, I'm homeless,
我和泰德之间的关系还是有点尴尬
things between me and Ted are still kind of weird.
所以有朋友陪伴真好
So, it's nice to be around friends.
你想住多久都行  宝贝
Well, stay as long as you want, sweetie.
谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
我给你买了本日记本
Now, I got you a journal.
我知道听起来很逊
I know this sounds lame,
但是把烦心事写下来  真的会有帮助
but it really helps work through stuff to write about it.
"亲爱的日记  干掉马修妈妈的幻想"
"Dear Diary. The fantasies of killing Marshall's mom
"变得越来越逼真了"
"have become more vivid.
"今天  我剥了她的头皮..."
"Today, I scalped her with a ..."
错了  那本是我的
Whoops, that one's mine.
这本给你
This is for you.
-你会在这玩得很开心的  -拜托  伙计们
- You are going to have so much fun here. - Oh, guys, please,
你们不必费心思要哄我开心
do not feel like you have to keep me entertained.
罗宾  如果你不想寻开心
Well, you shouldn't have come to East Meadow, Long Island,
就不要来长岛的东梅多
Robin, if you didn't want to be entertained.
真的吗  我过去以为这里没什么好玩的
Really? I didn't think there was a ton to do here.
显然是有人还没听说过
Oh, apparently, someone hasn't heard
尤宁古城的微缩模型博物馆
of the Uniondale Miniatures Museum.
你为了十九世纪的布艺慕名而来
You'll come for the 19th century thimble art,
而让你驻足的会是小瓶盖上画的荷兰大师们
but you'll stay for the Dutch masters on bottle caps.
另外  你还可以和两位
Plus, you'll be bowling with two
东梅多山猫队的创始人一起打保龄球
charter members of the East Meadow Alley Cats.
"我们是一支超爱热狗
"We're a hot dog eating team
外加沉迷保龄球的队伍"
with a bowling problem."
雪莉想出来的好梗
Shirley came up with that one.
雪莉是个保龄球高手
Great bowler, Shirley.
满分三百  她那天得了二百八
She hit 280 the other day.
可惜  是体重到达二百八
Unfortunately, that was on her bathroom scale.
罗宾搬出去后
When Robin moved out,
那间空卧室
there was a hole in my life
成了我生命中的空洞
in the shape of an empty bedroom.
我只好用新的嗜好来填补空洞
I filled it with a new hobby.
你在我原来的房间里干嘛
What are you doing in my old room?
这间房空着  让我心烦
This room being empty was bumming me out,
我决定找点健康的事做
so I decided to do something healthy
让我可以不去想你
that would take my mind off you.
在一个不通风的房间里
Well, nothing says healthy
一边熏着40磅的猪腰子
like smoking 40 pounds of pork loin in an unventilated room
一边幻想着在与前女友对话  可一点也不健康
while having an imaginary conversation with your ex.
就冲你这么说  不给你吃
Just for that, you're not getting any.
不给我吃是吧
I'm not getting any?
这房根本是在熏你的猪腰子
You're the one smoking your own meat.
我该拿昆茵怎么办
What am I gonna do about this Quinn thing?
我想再约她出来
I want to ask her out again,
但我不确定我介不介意她是脱衣舞女这事
but I don't know how I feel about her being a stripper.
你怎么会介意这个呢
Why would you have an issue with that?
我是说  你都跟重刑犯
I mean, you've dated convicted felons,
专门送自己的孩子  参加各类选拔赛事的妈妈
军火商  大赛妈妈们约会过
arms dealers, pageant moms.
我很可能会对昆茵动真情
Hey, Quinn is someone I might want to get serious with,
而不是假装自己是
not just pretend to be a judge
能帮助她四岁女儿当选小城小姐的裁判
who could help her four-year-old clinch Little Miss Biloxi.
蒂凡尼的妈妈为了那后冠真是使了浑身解数啊
Tiffany's mom really wanted that tiara.
在一个八百万人口的城市中
In a city of eight million people,
你恰好走进了她工作的舞厅
you happened to walk into the club where she works?
也许这就是命运
Maybe it's destiny.
不会  "命运"是甜瓜园舞厅的脱衣舞女
No, Destiny strips at The Melon Patch.
她们是人  泰德  尊重点搞搞清楚
They're people, Ted; try to keep them straight.
等等
Wait a minute.
如果这就是命运呢
What if this is destiny?
我刚说过...
I just said...
如果上天
What if the universe
安排我们相遇是有原因的呢
is throwing us in each other's path for some reason?
跟我刚说的差不多...
More or less exactly what I...
我不管你说了什么  这就是命运的安排
I don't care what you say, this is destiny!
该死的  泰德
Damn it, Ted!
你怎么就不相信真爱呢
Why can't you ever root for love?
昆茵
Quinn...
不  你听好
No, listen,
在这里就叫我卡玛  好吗
in here I'm Karma, okay?
好
Got it.
是这样  卡玛
Uh, look, Karma,
我发誓
I swear
我从没说过这些鬼话
I never say crap like this, but...
我想或许冥冥之中
I think maybe the universe is
上天自有安排
telling us something.
你想再跟我约会一次吗
You want to go out again?
抱歉  我不和客人约会
I'm sorry, I don't date customers.
那命运呢
What about Destiny?
我听说她跳槽去甜瓜园舞厅了
I heard she's over at The Melon Patch now.
不  我是说我们是天造地设的一对
No, I mean like fate telling us that we're supposed to be...
听着  巴尼
Oh, listen, Barney,
我的经理在狠狠瞪着我呢
my manager is really giving me the stink eye.
我得回去工作了
I have to get back to work.
好  等等  等等
Okay, wait, wait.
要是我付钱请你跳舞呢
What if I pay for a dance?
那样你的经理就高兴了
That way, your manager's happy,
然后我也能跟你解释
and then I can to tell you
为什么你得再和我约会一次
why you should go on another date with me.
听听也无妨
I guess there's no reason why not.
好的  首先  我们有很多共同点
Okay, first off, we have a lot in common.
比方说
For example,
咱俩的钱大多都是从
both of our jobs are largely financed
烂醉如泥的亚洲商人身上赚的
by drunk Asian businessmen.
亲爱的日记
Dear Diary.
今天是我岛上生活的第四天
It is day four on this island,
当地人都管这里叫"长"岛
which the natives have dubbed "Long Island,"
或许是因为
perhaps referencing
在这里时间漫"长"  度日如年吧
how each hour here feels like it may never end.
目前为止  他们欢迎了我的到来
So far, they have welcomed me
我也见识到些许他们的无聊生活
and given me a rare glimpse into their bizarre way of life.
"娱乐"  对于他们来说就是沙弧球
By "Entertainment," they mean table shuffle board,
绣花课  和其它毫无刺激的活动
macramé classes, and other non-stimulating activities
这些活动在曼哈顿
which are only used in Manhattan
只是用来镇定瘾君子或精神病罪犯的
to calm down drug addicts and the criminally insane.
这是一个没有文字的社会  他们的菜单上
A preliterate society, their menus display pictures
有的只是食物的图片
of the food they offer,
所有人都被迫一餐唱四五次
everyone is forced to sing "Happy Birthday"
生日快乐歌
four or five times a meal,
点心上还有烟花在燃烧
and dessert has fireworks in it.
在家中  他们常穿着名为"毛毯衫"的原始裹尸布
In their lairs, they often don a primitive shroud called a "Snugget,"
而且他们对每晚九点前上床习以为常
and it is not uncommon for them to go to sleep before 9 P.M.,
因为他们  害怕
fearing, as they do,
夜晚
the night.
还有  日记  我觉得写你真是犯傻
Also Diary, I think writing in you is stupid,
不过你是莉莉送的礼物
but you were a gift from Lily,
而且她正看着我
and she's watching me right now.
伙计们  我不好意思住太久
Guys, um, I don't want to overstay my welcome,
而且帕拉里斯让我去她那里住
and Patrice said that she would take me off your hands.
你们有没有火车时刻表或...
So, do you have a train schedule or...
有是有
Oh, yeah,
可...
um, but-but
火车出了点问题
there's a-a problem with the train.
大问题
Big, big problem.
发生了...
There was a...
-罢工  -是雷击[两者同字]
- Strike. - A lightning strike.
击中了一个正在罢工的纠察员
That hit one of the picketers who was on strike.
那时候下着雷雨
During a thunderstorm.
另外
Plus,
你不会想成为帕拉里斯的负担
you don't want to be a burden on Patrice.
对啊  她可能都不想你过去呢
Yeah, she probably doesn't even want you there.
你们怎么怪怪的
You guys are being weird.
天啊  罗宾  真抱歉
Oh, my God, Robin, I am so sorry.
我这就拿去洗
I'll throw these in the wash.
明天早上就能烘干叠整齐了
They'll be dry and folded in the morning.
或许得等周末
Or the weekend.
到时我们再谈你搬家的事吧
And we can talk about you leaving then.
或许永远不谈
Or never.
等等  莉莉  为什么不...
Wait, Lily, why don't...
八点三刻  该睡觉了
8:45, time to hit the hay.
晚安
Good night!
泰德  你在忙活什么
So Ted, what healthy,
健康得来又一点都不疯狂的活动啊
not-at-all-crazy activity are you up to now?
我之前喜欢玩熏肉  可现在我有新的爱好
I liked smoking meat, but now I've got a new passion:
木头
wood.
你听到了你自己说的傻话了吗
You hear these things that come out of your mouth, right?
于是我回到了情欲小野猫舞厅
So I went back to the Lusty Leopard.
你知道吗  巴尼
You know what, Barney?
我是说过我不和客人约会
I know I said I have a rule about not dating customers,
可你说服了我...
but you may have convinced me to...
曲子结束了  我得走了
Song's over, I got to go.
等等  别  什么  说服你什么
Wait, no, what? Convinced you to what?
抱歉  可我的经理正瞪着我
I'm sorry, but manager's giving me the stink eye.
别来烦我们了  经理
Ugh, get a life, Manager.
你刚才要说什么
What were you saying?
我正要说
Well, I was going to say
我真的发现你特别...有魅力
that I do find you very... charming.
幽默风趣
And funny...
还很性感
and sexy.
令人兴奋  聪明机智
And exciting and smart.
你真了解我
You so get me.
知道吗  巴尼
You know what, Barney?
我从来没这样过
I have never done this before,
可你有个特别之处...
but there's just something about you.
所以我想我的答案是...
So I guess my answer is...
曲子结束了
The song's over.
把你的想法说完
Well, just finish the thought!
-可经理不允许  -天啊
- But the manager. - God,
我恨经理
I hate manager.
给  你的答案是...
There. Your answer is...
我们真应该多了解一下彼此
We really need to know each other a little better.
给我说说你自己
Tell me about yourself.
我能对你说什么
Well, um, what can I tell you?
我...
I'm, um...
有魅力  幽默风趣
charming and funny
又性感  又...
and sexy and...
令人兴奋  又聪明机智
exciting and smart.
哪有姑娘能抵抗你这样的人啊
Well, how can a girl say no to that?
我们要不要...
How about we...
出去...
go out on...
这些曲子真是太短了
Ugh, these songs are so short.
你到底给了昆茵多少钱
Uh, how much exactly did you give Quinn?
八九百
Eight, nine hundred bucks,
外加我那只不记得价格的劳力士
plus whatever my Rolex is worth.
我知道
I know.
泰德  我觉得我恋爱了
Ted, I think I'm in love.
昆茵完全是在耍你
Quinn is totally playing you.
什么
What?
胡说八道
That's ridiculous.
如果她是在耍我
If she were playing me,
那为什么她会愿意和我约会
why would she agree to go on a date with me?
你不同于其他那些蠢货
You're different than the rest of these schlubs.
仅此一次  我要为你破例
This one time only, I'm going to break my rule.
明晚咱们出去吧
Let's go out tomorrow night.
太好了
Sweet!
糟糕
Oh, shoot.
明天我得工作
I have to work tomorrow. Ugh!
我有个好主意
Hey, brainstorm.
我们就在这里约会怎样
What if we just have our date here?
那就在这约会
It's a date.
那不是约会
It's not a date.
是你去脱衣舞厅  付钱看大腿舞
It's you going to a strip club and paying for lap dances!
如果不是约会  她为什么说跳四支舞送一支
If it's not a date, why'd she say every fifth dance was free?
这本来就是"情欲小野猫"周五晚上的特惠活动
Because that's the Lusty Leopard's policy on Friday nights,
居然我比你还了解  真是气死我了
and I'm so mad at you that I know that!
亲爱的日记
Dear Diary.
这是在长岛生活的第六天
It is day six on this island,
我开始觉得自己不像客人  更像是囚犯
and I begin to fear I am more captive than guest...
早上好  亲爱的
Morning, sweetie.
打门球吗
Up for croquet?
莉莉  你洗完我的衣服了吗  我得...
Hey, uh, Lil, are you done washing my clothes yet? Because I...
真是抱歉
Oh, I am so sorry.
你的衣服不幸被我装进
Your clothes accidentally wound up in the bag
捐给善心二手衣店的包里了
I donated to Goodwill.
你把我的衣服给捐了
You gave away my clothes?
你的衣服对东梅多的百姓来说  太华丽了
They were a bit fancy for East Meadow.
大家都盯着你看
People were staring.
另外  我们还有一件毛毯衫
Besides, we have an extra Snugget.
试试吧
Try it.
试试吧  罗宾
Try it, Robin.
他们试图把我同化  亲爱的日记
They're trying to make me one of them, Diary.
我开始害怕
And I begin to fear...
自己或许喜欢被同化
I may like it!
真不敢相信我们在脱衣舞厅
I can't believe we're at a strip club,
而这里最大的娘炮[波霸]就是你
and the biggest boob in here is you.
泰德  这是正式的约会
It's a real date, Ted.
显然你还没见到迪沙佛那对巨乳姐妹花
And clearly you haven't seen the DeSalvo twins.
她就在那边
She's right over there.
巴尼...  我擦咧
Barney... Yowza!
你不是在约会
You are not on a date.
那好  证明给我看
Okay, look, prove it.
证明她不是在利用你
Prove that she's not just taking advantage of you.
带她去别的地方约会
Get her to go out with you anywhere but here.
好吧
Fine!
帅哥  想来支舞不
Hey, sexy! You want a dance?
当然
Yeah!
不过有个条件
Uh, one thing, though.
我们去别的地方约会吧
Um, you'd be okay with us having a date
你没意见吧
somewhere besides here, wouldn't you?
就等你说这句话呢
I was hoping you would ask that.
抱歉这包厢价格太高了
I'm sorry it's so expensive in here,
但是这里舒适又没人打扰
but it's nice and private, huh?
没错  还很浪漫呢
Absolutely. And romantic!
这是我们第一次像情侣那样独处
It's our first getaway as a couple!
亲爱的日记  我清楚地意识到
It's become clear to me, Diary,
我必须得来一个绝命大逃亡
that I must attempt a dramatic escape.
我会在吃饭的时候假装胃疼
I will fake a stomachache during dinner.
然后趁马修和莉莉出门玩宾戈游戏的空档
Then, after Marshall and Lily leave for bingo night,
宾戈游戏  一种填写格子的游戏
在游戏中第一个成功者以喊"Bingo"表示取胜而得名
从后门溜走
I will sneak out the back.
我会偷走雪莉的车  直奔火车站
I'll swipe Shirley's Rascal and drive to the train station.
雪莉四十二岁  有一辆老人代步车
Shirley's 42, by the way, and rides a Rascal.
我发誓  这绝对堪比《机器人总动员》的下半部
I swear, it's the second half of Wall-E out here.
我就知道
Bingo...
宾戈游戏会取消
was canceled.
帅哥  想来支舞不
Hey, sexy, you want a dance?
不用了  我不是来光顾的
No, I'm not a customer.
我女朋友在这里工作
My girlfriend works here.
她在那儿...
She's right over...
仅此一次  我要为你破例
This one time only, I'm gonna break my rule.
明晚我们出去吧
Let's go out tomorrow night!
太好了
Sweet!
糟糕
Oh, shoot!
明天我得工作
I have to work tomorrow. Ugh!
我有个好主意
Hey! Brainstorm!
不如我们就在这里约会吧
What if we just have our date here,
进贵宾室喝点香槟  怎么样
maybe in the Champagne Room?
那是我们的专属地盘
That was our spot.
帅哥  想来支舞吗
Hey, gorgeous, You want a dance?
是快步舞吗
Is it a jig?
如果是  那该跳完了吧
'Cause if so, it's up.
抱歉  我只能靠《性感教师》最后的情节来铺梗骂你
Sorry, I only had the last verse of "Hot For Teacher" to work on that.
《性感教师》  范海伦乐队的歌曲
你刚算什么
What was that?
你对那个人分明是故技重施
You laid exactly the same line on that guy that you did on me!
亲爱的  那只是我说来哄那些好骗的废材而已
Sweetie, that is just something I say to these gullible losers here.
这招对他们屡试不爽
They fall for it every time.
一堆废材
Bunch of losers!
天啊  又是经理
Oh, gosh, manager again.
他看着我  好像在说
He's looking at me like,
"卡玛  为什么你不让贵宾室的客人加钟"
"Karma, why aren't you booking more time in the Champagne Room?"
我这就帮你加
Well, we'll show him.
不对  你又在耍我
No! You're playing me again!
你都舍不得花点心思
And you're not even trying hard!
经理根本不在  你指着的是一株植物
There's no manager there; You're pointing at a fern!
泰德说得对
Ted was right.
他现在肯定在家  嘲笑我多有傻
I bet he's home right now, laughing at how dumb I am.
我这算自食其果吧  绝对算
Did I deserve this? Absolutely.
我有时候是吹牛吹过了头
I have told some outrageous lies.
我说过自己是名人
I have told women I was famous,
战争英雄
a war hero,
和我上床可以治愈近视
that sex with me would cure their nearsightedness.
巴尼
Barney?!
是我活该  你对我做的一切再过分都不为过
I probably deserved everything you did to me and more.
但是我一直在努力
But I have been trying,
努力成为一个更好的人
and trying hard to be a better person.
谢谢你让我知道  我也曾是一个好人
Thanks for showing me I had it right before.
抱歉我们让你有点喘不过气
Look, I'm sorry we made you feel a little suffocated,
可你刚刚真是打算偷偷溜走吗
but were you really just gonna sneak away?
我只是想念城市的生活了
Well, it's just... I really miss the city.
我知道你们喜欢这里  这很好
I know you guys love it here, and that's fine,
我们不喜欢这里
We don't love it here!
什么
What?
拜托  罗宾
Come on, Robin,
这算什么生活啊
what kind of life is this?
参加凯纳斯特纸牌比赛
Going to canasta tournaments
凯纳斯特纸牌是是使用两组纸牌的桥牌游戏
还有高中曲棍球决赛
and high school field hockey playoffs?
我觉得北贝尔摩会称霸全州
Oh, I think North Bellmore can take state.
就索菲娅那踝关节  深表怀疑啊
With Sophie's ankle? Doubtful.
好吧  可如果你俩过得这么不快乐
Okay, but if you two are so unhappy,
何不直接搬回曼哈顿呢
why don't you just move back to Manhattan?
因为郊区更适合孩子啊
Because the suburbs are better for the baby.
谁说的  一个连你们自己都不快乐的地方
Who says? Who says any place is better for the baby
又怎么能适合孩子呢
if you two are unhappy in it?
不说了  我们现在定居在此了
No, no, we live here now.
而且  如果能有个朋友搬来长住的话
And, you know, this place wouldn't seem so bad
这里其实也没那么糟糕
if... we got one of our friends to move out here.
你们俩啊
Oh, guys...
那我还不如去自焚呢
I would rather set myself on fire.
第二天早上  巴尼发现
The next morning, Barney learned that
即使身处人口八百万的大都市
even in a city of eight million people,
也还是躲不开卡玛[报应]
there's no escaping Karma.
抱歉  不能闲聊  经理盯着呢
Sorry, can't talk; manager's watching.
如果我伤了你的心
Look, I am sorry
我很抱歉  那是工作需要
if I hurt your feelings; it's a job.
是吗  我的工作
Yeah, well, at my job,
就不会靠撕裂别人的心来赚钱
we don't rip out people's hearts for money.
我公司曾短暂支持过一个干这行的朝鲜实验室
My company briefly backed a lab in North Korea which did,
可我们卖掉它了
but we sold it!
我在那俱乐部工作了一整年
You know, I've worked at that club for a year.
你基本算那里的半个住客了
You practically live there,
可约会那天你都没认出我来
and you didn't even recognize me the night we went out.
所以别在我面前装什么受伤的乖宝宝
You can't pretend to be some hurt little victim with me.
我很了解你
I know you.
你当然了解我
Well, of course you do.
我把不为人知的事都告诉你了
I told you things I don't tell anybody.
我对你坦诚相见
I was honest with you.
没错  我会相信你有个黑人同志的哥哥
Yeah, because I believe you have a gay black brother,
有个寂寞到自制熏肉的好友
a friend lonely enough to smoke his own meat
还有个曾经追随超级游民乐队四处巡演的妈妈
and that your mom was a groupie for Supertramp.
那乐队就是以她而命名的
They named their band for her!
Supertramp也有超级荡妇之意
这些你都记得吗
You remembered all that?
没错
Well, yeah. I mean,
比起那首听过8000遍的
you're more interesting than the lyrics
"往我身上撒点糖"  你要有意思多了
to "Pour Some Sugar On Me" for the 8,000th time.
威豹乐队歌曲
真是讽刺
You know, it's funny.
几乎我遇到的所有女人
Almost every woman I've ever met was wrong
都错在让我有机可乘
to give me a chance.
你是第一个错在不给我机会的女人
You're the first woman who's wrong not to.
大杯黑咖啡
Large black coffee...
还有他点的东西
and whatever he's having.
都算在我账上
It's on me.
跟她要一样的
The same.
-谢了  -没事
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
再帮我买一千七百杯  咱们就扯平
1,700 more of these and we're even.
曲子刚好结束了
Uh, the song just ended.
是不是意味着你该走了
That mean you got to get going?
不
No.
你有时间陪我坐会儿吗
Do you have time to sit with me?
不知道  我的表还戴在你手上呢
I don't know. You're wearing my watch.
陶器  现在你又开始玩陶艺了
Pottery. Now you're making pottery.
人家需要个新花瓶
I needed a new vase...
还需要些盘子
and some plates.
和一些碗
And bowls.
我做的瓷器陈列橱设计不够稳妥
The china cabinet I built had some design flaws.
干嘛不直接把这房间弄成客房呢
Why don't you just turn this into a guest room?
客房
A guest room?
你是说弄成一间随时能住人
You mean a room ready and waiting
可住的那个人却不存在的房间吗
for someone who isn't there?
一间用来提醒我依旧孤身一人的房间吗
A room devoted to reminding me that I'm still alone?
我不需要那些
Yeah, I don't need that.
泰德  不管你往这个房间里堆多少东西
Ted, no matter how many things you put in this room...
我还是会占有一席之地
I'll still be here.
进来吧
Come on in.
谢了
Thanks.
谢谢你把我剩下的东西都收拾好
Oh, um, thanks for packing up the rest of my stuff.
不用谢  来点咖啡吗
No problem. Uh, you want some coffee?
-好啊  -好的
- Uh, sure. Yeah? - Yeah.
你过得如何
So, how are things?
-过得不错  你呢   -好极了
- Good! You? - Great!
-这马克杯其实是我亲手制作的  -是吗
- You know, I actually made this mug. - Oh, yeah?
抱歉  咖啡有点太猛了
Yeah, sorry, coffee's a little strong.
你在莉莉和马修家住得怎么样
How was your stay with Marshall and Lily?
有点怪怪的
Uh... A little weird.
其实他们不喜欢住在长岛
They're not loving Long Island.
我想他们内心深处已经意识到
I think deep down, they realize
那地方不适合他们
it just... isn't a good fit.
有时要承认这一点挺难的
It's hard to admit that sometimes.
的确如此
Sure is.
不过我想勇敢面对  跨过这道坎
But I guess it's better to face it and move on
也好过勉强自己委曲求全  对吧
than try to force something that just isn't meant to be, right?
深有同感
I think so.
没错
Yeah.
你准备如何处置我原来的房间
So, what do you think you're gonna do with my old room?
还没认真考虑过呢
Haven't really thought about it.
几天以后
谁稀罕曼哈顿啊
Who needs Manhattan?
没错
Yeah.
是泰德  他问我们
Hmm, it's Ted. He wants to know
想不想去市里玩
if we want to hang out in the city.
九分钟后有一趟车
The next train leaves in nine minutes.
亲爱的莉莉和马修  或许你们不知道
Dear Lily and Marshall, I don't know if you know this,
但我从未把你们的名字从租契上划掉
but I never took your names off the lease.
今天  我划掉我的名字
Well, today I took my name off it.
这间公寓现在归你们了
The apartment is now yours.
而且我想我终于找到
And I think I finally figured out
处置罗宾房间的最佳方法
the best thing to do with Robin's old room.
对我来说  如今总觉得这房间有旧情在牵绊
See, for me, this place has begun to feel a little haunted.
一开始  我以为是罗宾
At first, I thought it was haunted by Robin,
但现在我想其实是我自己
but now I think it was haunted by me.
不忘旧情事  难拥新生活
Well, no ghost is at peace until it finally moves on.
我需要改变
I need a change.
我想你们也一样
And I think you do, too.
这间公寓需要开始新的生活
This apartment needs some new life.
所以  请把我们的旧家  打造成你们的新家
So, please, make our old home your new home.
旧情自此断
It is now ghost-free.
爱你们的  泰德
Love, Ted.